<resources>
    <string name="app_name">SoftPowerButton</string>
    <string name="floating_button_window_launch_error">Failed to launch floating button.</string>
    <string name="floating_button_window_close_error">Failed to close floating button window</string>
    <string name="spb_notification_title">SoftPowerButton</string>
    <string name="spb_notification_desc">SoftPowerButton running…</string>
    <string name="spb_notification_channel_name">SoftPowerButton Channel</string>
    <string name="spb_notification_channel_description">Notification channel for SoftPowerButton</string>
    <string name="dismiss">Dismiss</string>
    <string name="stop_all">Stop all</string>
    <string name="ok">OK</string>
    <string name="overlay_permission_request">Allow SoftPowerButton to draw over your apps to be enable display a floating easy
        access button.</string>
    <string name="spb_device_admin">SoftPowerButton device admin</string>
    <string name="spb_device_admin_description">SoftPowerButton device admin implementation to enable an instant screen lock feature.</string>
    <string name="add_admin_extra_app_explanation">This permission needs to be granted to enable SoftPowerButton initiate
        lock screen when you ask it to. Please ignore the danger warning afterwards. This app is safe and open source.</string>
    <string name="device_admin_permission_rejected_warning">Device admin permission rejected. SoftPowerButton will not be able to lock screen on command.
        SoftPowerButton will not be able to lock screen on command. Close the floating button to request again.</string>
    <string name="accessibility_service_description">SoftPowerButton accessibility service to enable it perform an accessibility action</string>
    <string name="reboot_confirm">Are you sure you want to restart phone?</string>
    <string name="yes">Yes</string>
    <string name="title_activity_test">TestActivity</string>
    <string name="accessibility_service_not_enabled">Power menu couldn\'t be shown because the app\'s accessibility service is not enabled.</string>
    <string name="enable_text">Enable</string>
    <string name="overlay_permission_rejected">Overlay permission rejected. SoftPowerButton will not be able to show on the screen.</string>
    <string name="accessibility_service_instr">To show the power menu for restart, etc, enable accessibility service for this app.</string>
    <string name="accessibility_not_enabled_warning">Accessibility service for SoftPowerButton needs to be enabled to be able to show power menu, lock screen and listen to volume keys</string>
    <string name="cancel">Cancel</string>
    <string name="accessibility_guide">If you are on the accessibility settings page, go to \'More downloaded services\' or \'Downloaded apps\' and locate SoftPowerButton. Click on it and enable it\'s accessibility service.</string>
    <string name="floating_dialog_close_error">Failed to close floating dialog window.</string>
    <string name="floating_dialog_window_launch_error">Failed to launch floating dialog.</string>
    <string name="sleep_screen">Sleep</string>
    <string name="power_menu">Power menu</string>
    <string name="close">Close</string>
    <string name="enable_accessibility_service_screen_lock">Enable accessibility service for SoftPowerButton in order to lock screen.</string>
    <string name="enable_accessibility_service_power_menu">Enable accessibility service for SoftPowerButton to show power menu for restart.</string>
    <string name="stop_service_shortcut_label">Stop service.</string>
    <string name="stop_service_shortcut_label1">Stop accessibility service to enable you uninstall the app.</string>
    <string name="general_guide">Welcome to the SoftPowerButton guide.\n\n\nSoftPowerButton offers all the functionalities
        of your real power button whether it\'s broken or not.\nThis means you can do all the things you used to do with your real power button using this app.\n\n
        The functionalities includes:\n\n
        1. Sleep\/Lock your phone screen by clicking the floating button once.\n\n
        2. Show the power menu to access the reboot button and others by long pressing on the floating button.\n\n
        3. Wake up the phone by clicking on your volume buttons.\n\n
        4. Easily access these features anywhere with the floating widget and tray notification.\n\n
        5. Easily access these features from your locked screen using the lock screen notification.\n\n
        6. Take screenshots by clicking on the floating button twice.\n\n
        Note: If your phone powered off and your real power button is broken, you can start the app by pressing both volume buttons
        while you insert a USB cable into it\'s port at the same time. The phone\'s recovery menu will be shown to you.
        Use the volume button to navigate to \'Reboot\' and wait or just wait for the phone to put it in reboot mode.
        After a while your phone will automatically reboot itself.\n\n\n
        Other Instructions\n\n\n
        1. To close or hide the floating power button, drag the button unto the white close icon.\n\n
        2. To uninstall the app, click on \'Stop all\' in the notification or long press app icon to reveal
        a shortcut to click on. After this, try to uninstall.\n\n
    </string>
    <string name="uninstall_ready">App is now ready to uninstall.</string>
</resources>